The next question is from NYX22.
Mr. Avila, are you scared for your life and is Brazil protecting you?
Thank you for bringing that up, NYX22.
We always discuss this on the boat, Amanda,
that people were discussing when we were like two days before interception.
And people were saying, are you scared to everyone?
And most of the people would say, no, I'm more scared of not fulfilling our mission,
of living our life in vain, of the future that my daughter will live at.
So I'm much more concerned for the future generations than for anyone's life.
We need to do this. It's our historical duty to do so.
So we have a very serious risk assessment.
I train our participants in nonviolence direct action
and how they need to behave in case of an interception, for example,
to escalate stuff.
So we take this very, very seriously, but we do not stop for that.
Otherwise, what would be the history of humanity
if people would stop doing something important because it's dangerous?
So we need to understand this danger, work with it,
and try to neutralize as many dangers as we can
and try to reduce the impact of the damage that we cannot neutralize and continue.
And Brazil is not protecting me at all.
Actually, Brazil didn't break relations with Israel,
despite the fact that they kidnapped the Brazilian system.
We get it. We understand what you're saying.
Putting on solitary confinement.
That was very diplomatic.
But Brazil is an ally of the Palestinian cause
and it still has contradictions,
but at least on speech,
President Lula gives very good speeches denouncing the genocide.
We get it.
We understand what you're saying.
That was very diplomatic.
Amen.